const o="BB 25",i="bgs",n=[{number:1,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:2,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:3,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:4,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:5,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:6,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:7,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:8,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:9,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:10,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:11,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:12,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:13,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:14,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:15,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:16,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:17,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:18,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:19,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:20,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:21,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:22,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:23,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:24,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:25,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:26,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:27,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:28,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:29,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""},{number:30,question:"$Question$",image:null,optionA:"$Option A$",optionA_img:null,optionB:"$Option B$",optionB_img:null,optionC:"$Option C$",optionC_img:null,optionD:"$Option D$",optionD_img:null,answer:""}],t={board:o,subject:"bgs",questions:n};export{o as board,t as default,n as questions,i as subject};
